<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Driving in Cars With Bears on The Big Ugly House Blog</title>
    <link>http://bears.cookwithchef.com/tags/driving-in-cars-with-bears/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Driving in Cars With Bears on The Big Ugly House Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 01:03:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://bears.cookwithchef.com/tags/driving-in-cars-with-bears/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 8</title>
      <link>http://bears.cookwithchef.com/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 01:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bears.cookwithchef.com/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-8/</guid>
      <description>The bear is dirty. The bear is why you can’t keep clean.  Plot Summary  While analysing some of the bear scat that they had retrieved, Dave and his lab friends find human flesh in some of the samples. This is puzzling however, since the samples did notcome from locations where people have been reported missing. Recognizing the urgency of the situation, Dave suggests placing a bounty on bears for hunters, and the government was quick to approve this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://bears.cookwithchef.com/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 02:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bears.cookwithchef.com/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;  A line from which there can be no return  Plot Summary  The local media is abuzz with news of the bear attacks. One victim of the bear attacks was “Jessie Black of Deer Lake, the reigning queen of the Lomond River Golf Club’s par-three sixth hole.” What. What does that mean.   The Northern Examiner gives it to us straight: “BAD-ASSED BEAR NEWS: IT’S BAD, REAL BAD” reporting, “This is the most serious blow to the industry since the 9/11 terrorist attack.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>