<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Big Ugly House Blog</title>
    <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Big Ugly House Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 00:35:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 13</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-13-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 00:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-13-draft/</guid>
      <description>This “crazy” who you’re talking about is a genius. A real genius. &amp;nbsp; Dave and Kim piece together that the fancy human meatballs are being used to deter the bears from eating people. They take a team to go tranquilize a bear and bring it back to the lab. In their TRUCK, obviously because that’s just what you do when you want to get a bear from point A to point B, you just put it in the backseat of your car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dishwashers are overrated</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/dishwashers-are-overrated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 22:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/dishwashers-are-overrated/</guid>
      <description>Washing a dish takes 10 seconds. Putting a dish in the dishwasher takes 7 seconds. 3 seconds is nothing. You can keep standing straight up to wash dishes in the sink. You have to bend over to put something in the dishwasher. Dishes in the dish drying rack are always clean, so you can get into a habit of putting a dish or two away whenever you are waiting for something on the stove.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 12</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 00:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-12/</guid>
      <description>The bear was his only friend now. Plot Summary Chapter 12 opens with Norm Cotten’s suggestion that Jack take some time off to be with his wife. This makes Jack furious, naturally. While Jack is away on unspecified business, Starlight breaks into the house and kills Dorothy.  Jack approves. A bear’s gotta do what a bear’s gotta do. Jack cries, but “not the tears of grief, but of the same old hatred and rage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 11</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 23:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-11/</guid>
      <description>They’re the most wild. The most alive when they’re wild, the most alive when they’re free, and no bear’s gonna be cooped up for long, you better believe that. Plot Summary Dorothy and Jack’s marriage continues to disintegrate. Dorothy sees Starlight hanging out on the veranda, and exclaims “Jack! The bear is on the veranda”. Jack, who was dozing in front of the six o’clock news, like a parody of a man utterly disillusioned of life, wakes to Dorothy’s distress thinking “Oh boy, what now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 11</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-11-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 01:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-11-draft/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 11 &amp;nbsp; They’re the most wild. The most alive when they’re wild, the most alive when they’re free, and no bear’s gonna be cooped up for long, you better believe that. &amp;nbsp; Dorothy and Jack’s marriage continues to disintegrate. Dorothy sees Starlight hanging out on the veranda, and exclaims “Jack! The bear is on the veranda”. Jack, who was dozing in front of the six o’clock news, like a parody of a man utterly disillusioned of life, wakes to Dorothy’s distress thinking “Oh boy, what now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapters 9 and 10</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapters-9-and-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 01:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapters-9-and-10/</guid>
      <description>But who? How? This is such a small place and everyone knows everyone else. How could they get away with it? Plot Summary More bear attacks! Two boys are attacked and the parents of the boys sue the province for gross negligence. The Northern Examinerreleases another on-point headline: “Grossed out at Gros Morne national park bear lunch.”  A town meeting is held with everyone being angry at the park and government officials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 8</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 01:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-8/</guid>
      <description>The bear is dirty. The bear is why you can’t keep clean. Plot Summary While analysing some of the bear scat that they had retrieved, Dave and his lab friends find human flesh in some of the samples. This is puzzling however, since the samples did notcome from locations where people have been reported missing. Recognizing the urgency of the situation, Dave suggests placing a bounty on bears for hunters, and the government was quick to approve this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 7</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 02:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-7/</guid>
      <description>Theirs was a friendship forged from the intensity of a daring and dangerous encounter Chapter 7 introduces us to our new hero, Dave Bishop, Ph.D, who works for the National Parks and Wildlife Department. We get to know Dave pretty well this chapter, as we hear all about his “trim, youthful physique and professorial manner,” “rugged disposition” and how “his face reflected an intense mental alertness and a focused gaze. He was all business, ready, decisive; there wasn’t much about him that went unnoticed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 6</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 02:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; A line from which there can be no return Plot Summary The local media is abuzz with news of the bear attacks. One victim of the bear attacks was “Jessie Black of Deer Lake, the reigning queen of the Lomond River Golf Club’s par-three sixth hole.” What. What does that mean.  The Northern Examiner gives it to us straight: “BAD-ASSED BEAR NEWS: IT’S BAD, REAL BAD” reporting, “This is the most serious blow to the industry since the 9/11 terrorist attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 6</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-6-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 02:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-6-draft/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; A line from which there can be no return The media is abuzz with bear attack news. One victim of the bear attacks was “Jessie Black of Deer Lake, the reigning queen of the Lomond River Golf Club’s par-three sixth hole.” What. What does that mean.  One newspaper reports “BAD-ASSED BEAR NEWS: IT’S BAD, REAL BAD” reporting, “This is the most serious blow to the industry since the 9/11 terrorist attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 5</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 00:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>Plot summary Jack keeps feeding the bears and is training them to respond to commands. ~*Winter passes*~ In the spring, the male bear has come out of hibernation, but Jack finds the lady bear dead from a vicious attack. Jack and Norm are becoming annoyed with one another. Assorted thoughts  Jack likes taking care of the orphaned bears because “it was nice to be needed”. Ummm...paralyzed wife might need you a bit, dude?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 4</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 02:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Don&#39;t feed the bears (human flesh). Plot Summary Dorothy “Plot Point” Crandall has a stroke and is partially paralyzed. To pay for Dorothy’s medical care, Jack and Dorothy sell the lodge and Jack gets a job full time at the funeral home. One day, out and about in town, Jack is enraged to see Rick Preston back in town with another outfitter. Jack has to pick up a corpse at the county morgue and bring back to the funeral home to cremate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 3</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 00:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Plot Sumarry Chapter 3 basically deals with the court case against Jack, who is being held liable for Rick’s illegal killing of the bear cub. Jack hires a lawyer and has his day in court, but ultimately, the judge rules against him, stripping him of his outfitters license.  Assorted thoughts  This chapter doesn’t have anything too crazy in it--it’s just there to move the plot along to where Jack is no longer an outfitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 2</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 00:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Plot Summary In Chapter 2, Jack receives word that he is to be held responsible for Rick’s illegal killing of the bear cub. This puts his business at risk, and puts him in a precarious financial position. He also has funeral costs for Calvin to consider. He discusses funeral arrangements with Norm, who pushes for cremation. He also offers to perform Calvin’s ceremony for free, and offers Jack a job at the funeral home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 1</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/the-gros-morne-justice-story-chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 03:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/the-gros-morne-justice-story-chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Plot Summary Chapter 1 opens with a picturesque description of the Crandall residence. We meet our hero Jack, his wife Dorothy, and their son Calvin, who currently works at a funeral home, in addition to helping out with his father’s outfitting business. The wealthy Americans arrive, and after one day of hunting, all but one of the hunters has killed a bear. Rick, the leader of the American group, is completely soured by not having bagged a bear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Part 2 (UPDATE)</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/the-gros-morne-justice-story-part-2-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 03:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/the-gros-morne-justice-story-part-2-update/</guid>
      <description>We did some digging to find out more about Ed Asner, of the mysterious celebrity review. &amp;nbsp;  ED ASNER IS A 911 TRUTHER  what does it mean terrorism doesn’t rhyme with bearorism for no reason What is the connection between bears and 911? This is the central question here.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Part 2 (Celebrity review)</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/the-gros-morne-justice-story-part-2-celebrity-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 04:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/the-gros-morne-justice-story-part-2-celebrity-review/</guid>
      <description>The plot thickens before we even begin the story itself. The very first page of the book, a review by Ed Asner, actor, hints at the dark secrets within.  “What a provocative idea! I found the novel fascinating … an intriguing story. It bears (no pun intended) not only further reading, but further investigation. A cautionary note: Don’t have anyone read this book to President George Bush and Homeland Security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Part 1</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/the-gros-morne-justice-story-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 03:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/the-gros-morne-justice-story-part-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; Have you ever read a book with plot turns so swift and surprising that you needed to put the book down multiple times to catch your breath? That was our experience just reading the back cover of Gros Morne Justice: A Bear Romantic Comedy Buddy Cop Political Intrigue Survival Thriller. Take a look:   &amp;nbsp; We found this gem at a yard sale on our way back from a camping trip on the Fundy coast of New Brunswick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An exciting oval shape</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/an-exciting-oval-shape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 23:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/an-exciting-oval-shape/</guid>
      <description>Egg person? Egg Person??!!  Are you trying to give me nightmares?   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanz the pigeon</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/hanz-the-pigeon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 15:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/hanz-the-pigeon/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clarence the chicken</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/clarence-the-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 16:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/clarence-the-chicken/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>