<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>You Mustnt Get Excited Dear on The Big Ugly House Blog</title>
    <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/tags/you-mustnt-get-excited-dear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in You Mustnt Get Excited Dear on The Big Ugly House Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 23:19:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/tags/you-mustnt-get-excited-dear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 11</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 23:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-11/</guid>
      <description>They’re the most wild. The most alive when they’re wild, the most alive when they’re free, and no bear’s gonna be cooped up for long, you better believe that. Plot Summary Dorothy and Jack’s marriage continues to disintegrate. Dorothy sees Starlight hanging out on the veranda, and exclaims “Jack! The bear is on the veranda”. Jack, who was dozing in front of the six o’clock news, like a parody of a man utterly disillusioned of life, wakes to Dorothy’s distress thinking “Oh boy, what now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapters 9 and 10</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapters-9-and-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 01:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapters-9-and-10/</guid>
      <description>But who? How? This is such a small place and everyone knows everyone else. How could they get away with it? Plot Summary More bear attacks! Two boys are attacked and the parents of the boys sue the province for gross negligence. The Northern Examinerreleases another on-point headline: “Grossed out at Gros Morne national park bear lunch.”  A town meeting is held with everyone being angry at the park and government officials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 8</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 01:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-8/</guid>
      <description>The bear is dirty. The bear is why you can’t keep clean. Plot Summary While analysing some of the bear scat that they had retrieved, Dave and his lab friends find human flesh in some of the samples. This is puzzling however, since the samples did notcome from locations where people have been reported missing. Recognizing the urgency of the situation, Dave suggests placing a bounty on bears for hunters, and the government was quick to approve this.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>