<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terrible Ideas on The Big Ugly House Blog</title>
    <link>http://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/docs/tags/terrible-ideas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Terrible Ideas on The Big Ugly House Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 02:34:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/docs/tags/terrible-ideas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 6</title>
      <link>http://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/docs/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 02:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/docs/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; A line from which there can be no return Plot Summary The local media is abuzz with news of the bear attacks. One victim of the bear attacks was “Jessie Black of Deer Lake, the reigning queen of the Lomond River Golf Club’s par-three sixth hole.” What. What does that mean.  The Northern Examiner gives it to us straight: “BAD-ASSED BEAR NEWS: IT’S BAD, REAL BAD” reporting, “This is the most serious blow to the industry since the 9/11 terrorist attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 4</title>
      <link>http://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/docs/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 02:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/docs/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Don&#39;t feed the bears (human flesh). Plot Summary Dorothy “Plot Point” Crandall has a stroke and is partially paralyzed. To pay for Dorothy’s medical care, Jack and Dorothy sell the lodge and Jack gets a job full time at the funeral home. One day, out and about in town, Jack is enraged to see Rick Preston back in town with another outfitter. Jack has to pick up a corpse at the county morgue and bring back to the funeral home to cremate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 2</title>
      <link>http://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/docs/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 00:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/docs/posts/gros-morne-justice-chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Plot Summary In Chapter 2, Jack receives word that he is to be held responsible for Rick’s illegal killing of the bear cub. This puts his business at risk, and puts him in a precarious financial position. He also has funeral costs for Calvin to consider. He discusses funeral arrangements with Norm, who pushes for cremation. He also offers to perform Calvin’s ceremony for free, and offers Jack a job at the funeral home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Part 2 (Celebrity review)</title>
      <link>http://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/docs/posts/the-gros-morne-justice-story-part-2-celebrity-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 04:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://beethacker.github.io/bigugly/docs/posts/the-gros-morne-justice-story-part-2-celebrity-review/</guid>
      <description>The plot thickens before we even begin the story itself. The very first page of the book, a review by Ed Asner, actor, hints at the dark secrets within.  “What a provocative idea! I found the novel fascinating … an intriguing story. It bears (no pun intended) not only further reading, but further investigation. A cautionary note: Don’t have anyone read this book to President George Bush and Homeland Security.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>