<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uncategorized on The Big Ugly House Blog</title>
    <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/categories/uncategorized/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uncategorized on The Big Ugly House Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 00:35:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/categories/uncategorized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 13</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-13-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 00:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-13-draft/</guid>
      <description>This “crazy” who you’re talking about is a genius. A real genius. &amp;nbsp; Dave and Kim piece together that the fancy human meatballs are being used to deter the bears from eating people. They take a team to go tranquilize a bear and bring it back to the lab. In their TRUCK, obviously because that’s just what you do when you want to get a bear from point A to point B, you just put it in the backseat of your car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 11</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-11-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 01:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-11-draft/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 11 &amp;nbsp; They’re the most wild. The most alive when they’re wild, the most alive when they’re free, and no bear’s gonna be cooped up for long, you better believe that. &amp;nbsp; Dorothy and Jack’s marriage continues to disintegrate. Dorothy sees Starlight hanging out on the veranda, and exclaims “Jack! The bear is on the veranda”. Jack, who was dozing in front of the six o’clock news, like a parody of a man utterly disillusioned of life, wakes to Dorothy’s distress thinking “Oh boy, what now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gros Morne Justice: Chapter 6</title>
      <link>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-6-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 02:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beethacker.github.io/bigugly_hugo/posts/chapter-6-draft/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; A line from which there can be no return The media is abuzz with bear attack news. One victim of the bear attacks was “Jessie Black of Deer Lake, the reigning queen of the Lomond River Golf Club’s par-three sixth hole.” What. What does that mean.  One newspaper reports “BAD-ASSED BEAR NEWS: IT’S BAD, REAL BAD” reporting, “This is the most serious blow to the industry since the 9/11 terrorist attack.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>